<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Projects on AntVD.site</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/projects/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Projects on AntVD.site</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 30 Jan 2024 12:51:57 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/projects/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Imagine: Impossible Gamepads</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/projects/2024-01-30-imagine-impossible-gamepads/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Jan 2024 12:51:57 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/projects/2024-01-30-imagine-impossible-gamepads/</guid>
      <description>w﻿ith Midjourney getting even more advanced, here&amp;rsquo;s a showcase of some impossible gamepads.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Imagine: Star Wars: Shinkai Edition</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/projects/2023-04-24-imagine-star-wars-shinkai-edition/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Apr 2023 21:03:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/projects/2023-04-24-imagine-star-wars-shinkai-edition/</guid>
      <description>T﻿his is the first of a series of Imagine projects, a collection of images mixing two different concepts together in interesting ways, using Midjourney as the driving engine.&#xA;Makoto Shinkai&amp;rsquo;s movies have some of the best skies and colour palette in any anime, and Star Wars feels like the perfect franchise for Shinkai to create something beautiful.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Synthetic Art - Fashionable Weaponry</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/projects/synthetic-art-fashionable-weaponry/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Nov 2022 23:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/projects/synthetic-art-fashionable-weaponry/</guid>
      <description>One of the cool things that AI generated art lets you do is quickly imagine how different concepts would work in real life.&#xA;Take for example the video game franchise Borderlands, there are various weaponry created by certain brands that in turn make them distinctive:&#xA;This is an imagining of that concept using real world brands.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Synthetic Art - Midjourney V4</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/projects/synthetic-art/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Nov 2022 18:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/projects/synthetic-art/</guid>
      <description>Midjourney recently released their Version 4 model, and already you can see marked improvements, specifically in regards to anime stills.&#xA;This is some of the latest works that I&amp;rsquo;ve created using the new model. You can tell that there&amp;rsquo;s more emphasis on the bloom within the new imagery.&#xA;Currently the images are limited to 1:1 ratio images, but I&amp;rsquo;m hoping that changes soon.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Synthetic Art</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/projects/synthetic-art-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Oct 2022 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/projects/synthetic-art-1/</guid>
      <description>In the last year AI image generation has improved leaps and bounds, and in turn I&amp;rsquo;ve been exploring the possibilities of Midjourney, since it&amp;rsquo;s public release, earlier this year.&#xA;There&amp;rsquo;s a lot to be said about the intricacies and ethical questions regarding AI&amp;rsquo;s role in the art world, but ultimately it&amp;rsquo;s a tool, much like Photoshop. While I still need to dig deeper into the curation, it&amp;rsquo;s entirely possible to find a resonance, narrative and personal style of your own through the tool.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Anime Colour Grading</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/projects/anime-colour-grading/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Jul 2020 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/projects/anime-colour-grading/</guid>
      <description>Anime backgrounds tend to be these beautiful, coloured backdrops that have this hyper-realistic quality to them. One particular style brought by artist/animator/director Makoto Shinkai, are particularly impressive, with his films such as 5 Centimeters per Second and Your Name both showing landscapes in a truly impressive way.&#xA;There&amp;rsquo;s also Miyazaki&amp;rsquo;s Studio Ghibli, whose films such as My Neighbor Totoro, Spirited Away and Howl’s Moving Castle all feature iconic grass plains, lush forests and expansive coastlines.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tiltshift</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/projects/tiltshift/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 May 2020 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/projects/tiltshift/</guid>
      <description>This is a growing collection if images digitally edited in the style of Tiltshift photography.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hellotickets Redesign Concepts</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/projects/hellotickets-redesign-concepts/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Mar 2020 09:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/projects/hellotickets-redesign-concepts/</guid>
      <description>With the help of our product designer, these concepts were created to give credence to his ideas and plan for Hellotickets&amp;rsquo; imagery to represent each city or activity.&#xA;Using stock and royalty-free imagery and Photoshop, the idea was to take the most iconic or recognizable feature of a city, and place that upon a preconceived solid background, that represented a general &amp;ldquo;type of activity&amp;rdquo;.&#xA;While the final images, proved to be much more simple affairs, here is where you can see the concept images of what could be possible using this method.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Website Creation</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/projects/websites/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/projects/websites/</guid>
      <description>Smash Cow Smash Cow is a burger joint in my home town, whose website I offered to tweak after seeing it. The site is built with Squarespace to allow them to edit content at an easier pace. It&amp;rsquo;s built using Squarespace 7.1, which allows for a certain level customizability, with CSS allowing for customization beyond what Squarespace allows.&#xA;The logo itself has a strong relation to neon, and my favourite part of tweaking the website was coding the buttons to have a neon effect with reflection.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Skylines</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/projects/skylines/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/projects/skylines/</guid>
      <description>A collection of landscapes and seascapes shot during my travels.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
